Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
NO ANIMALS WERE HARMED DURING
THE FILMING OF THIS PRODUCTION.
That's how my father sees fit, Osman Bey.
Allah is with those who have patience.
May I come in, son?
I wish to be alone, aunt.
Aren't you alone in a crowded place, if you
can't be together with your loved one, son?
Does it matter if I'm here or not?
My heart aches every time
I think about it.
Why doesn't he see me worthy
of his daughter?
What did I do wrong for him
to not see me as a man?
It's not about being a man, son.
Sheikh Edebali knows your manliness, your
courage the best.
What really matters is what
you're going to do now.
Will you let your anger get
the better of you...
... or will you overcome it and
proceed with your mind?
That's what this is all about.
It looks like winter will be harsh.
We need to work hard. We also need to take
care of the poor.
We shall prepare the shoes, hats, and
vests to be handed out.
We'll get through this if Allah permits.
It's okay.
It didn't burn, don't worry.
No visible burns, but...
... the fire is deep inside.
Bala. Every cloud has a silver lining.
What matters is seeing the good in
my Sheikh's decision.
I don't know the reason or the outcome of
this decision.
I only know one thing.
My heart pumps for Osman now.
If I have to wait, I shall spend
my life waiting.
Waiting is tough, but it's worth it
if I'm waiting for Osman.
If we're talking about Osman, you won't be
waiting for long.
He'll find a way.
It's a weird feeling.
It's snowing on me, but my insides
are burning.
I don't know if I'm cold, or if I'm
burning. But my father has the answers.
I'll go talk to him.
- Welcome, my daughter.
- Thank you, father.
Nights are longer now, I thought you
might be hungry.
Thank you, that's nice of you, my Bala.
It's important to know the right time, to
wait for the right time.
In these lands, almond trees bloom, all
of a sudden...
... thinking the spring has come, my
daughter.
They get fooled by the fake sunlight, and
by the warmth of the branches.
But instead, because it wasn't the right
time, all they get is the night's cold.
Time is also important in relationships.
You shall protect your fresh leaves,
your essence that I worked hard on...
... from the winter sun.
Protect them, so that winter's cold
can't burn your flowers.
I don't want you to talk to Osman.
Remember that.
Bala!
What happened, Bala? Are you okay?
My father doesn't want me to
talk with Osman.
He has made his decision, Gonca.
He has made his decision.
Once upon a time, there was a beautiful
young lady, and a brave young man.
My Rab made them meet each
other using a deer.
They fell in love the moment they saw
each other.
I can't tell you all of them, son. They
fought such troubles.
But they never gave up on their love.
That love came to life, became three
brave little valiants.
Gündüz, Savcı, and you.
Now how can you be upset like that?
Tell me.
My heart is a battlefield, aunt.
My loved one is besides me, but
I can't pull her closer.
It's not anger, not greed.
But...
Not being able to come together
drives me crazy.
May I come in, my Bey?
Come in, Konur Alp.
My Bey...
Your fires hurt me as well.
I couldn't stay in the Alp Tent,
I came here.
Give the orders, and we shall
take off, my Bey.
Since she also loves you, let's kidnap
Bala Hatun, my Bey.
I like disorder but everything got
out of hand this time.
In this chaos, the biggest duty
is yours, Sofia.
As long as our aims win, father.
Alişar is the only power who can
defeat Kayıs without using weapons.
For this reason, his allience is crucial.
Don't tire yourself anymore, sir.
What you're trying to say is understood.
May others help you as well, son.
Your grandsons shall respect you too, son.
Thank you, my Bey father.
May Allah accept your prayers.
Is there anything wrong
in the Tent, Yaman?
Everything is fine, my Bey.
But I heard something at night.
You, my Yaman, stay still like an owl, but
you don't miss a single thing.
Tell me, what is it?
Osman has sent Selcan Hatun to ask Sheikh
Edebali permission to marry his daughter.
What did he say?
Didn't allow it.
Sheikh Edebali didn't even bother.
That's what happens if you send your
aunt, instead of your Tent's Bey uncle.
Now Osman can cry on his own.
- May I come in, uncle?
- Come in, my nephew.
Is it good news, this early in
the morning?
A caravan's status came in from our
scout Alps along the border.
Departed from Nikea, I suppose they
are going to Kulucahisar.
The good news keeps on coming.
Are they loaded?
Carrier-full.
They are trying to hide it but, they are
ready for battle.
Do you think they are preparing
for battle, my Bey?
Silently. They smile at our faces, but
they are preparing for battle.
- What is your order?
- It's certain...
... that everyone shows their
true colours, my nephew.
- So will we.
- Are we, going to attack the castle?
No. Not now. Not now
First, we'll attack the caravan and
strangle the castle for a little while.
They think Dündar Bey forgot.
But they don't know that
I don't forget anything!
Kidnapping my daughter and torturing
Osman. They will pay for both of them.
- They will pay for it.
- I should tell Osman to prepare with his Alps.
No no. No need.
My brave son Batur will take care of this.
We don't attack the enemy in
such a way lately.
Now go and show them who
Dündar Bey's son Batur Alp is.
Bring the bounty here so Kayı Beys
see a valiant!
Your wish is my command, my Bey.
Friends, it's now obvious that before
we destroy the evil in Kulucahisar...
... we can't rest in these lands.
Are we going to migrate, my Sheikh?
We'll make these lands our
country, Zülfikar.
We'll go for a fight.
Surviving in these lands is tough, my
Sheikh. One needs strong allies.
Banner Lord Alişar is Konya's man
from the Mongolian attacks.
While Ertuğrul Bey isn't here, Dündar Bey
won't side with us.
Osman on the other hand...
And we didn't let Osman marry
our daughter.
Who are we going to do this with, you're
saying, right Fakı?
I couldn't say it myself, master.
That's what we lack.
We don't ask for anyone's approval. Only
Allah giveth.
For this reason, we'll move to Yenipazar.
As stronger, more stable.
We'll let Muslims breathe with
our craftsmanship.
- Pehlivan.
- Yes, sir.
- Zülfikar.
- Yes, my Sheikh.
Send the news to Tekeli, Konya, and
Kayseri.
They shall wake up. Our friends with Ahi's
spirit in their hearts shall get on the road.
It's time for us to bless these wild
grass-covered lands with roses of faith.
- Yes, my Sheikh.
- Yes, master.
Do you see the silks, the cloths?
- Suits my Bey well.
- Same with the ones in the castle.
Alişar Bey's mansion is no different
from a palace. Right, Nizamettin?
Correct, my Bey.
Why are you upset?
Your Beylic's intentions are no good.
What are you talking about? What do you
mean they are no good?
While you were in Konya, Osman and
Kulucahisar issue reignited.
Nizamettin, Nizamettin.
You think you're gathering news. I know
what Osman is doing.
I know about the rest. Osman's Alps died.
His intentions are certain.
Killing Sofia and Kalonoz.
And, my Bey, Sofia wants to visit you
in your mansion.
It's obvious that it's about this issue.
I like the silky ones and the
ones with flowers.
Tell the princess she can come.
I smell like a goat thanks to all
those migrating ones! Zorba!
Prepare the bathhouse!
My Osman. Don't be angry at yourself for
this love matter.
It doesn't suit a man.
It's not just about love, Bamsı Bey.
Son, then tell this old man Bamsı Bey what
is bothering you.
Sheikh Edebali is pushing me off.
He doesn't see me worthy of a
conversation.
Son, Sheikh Edebali is a noble one.
Friendship with a noble one is hard. It's
probably for good reason, son.
Keep your eyes open, son. It's not the
time to spread sadness.
Look, a caravan is coming to Kulucahisar
from Nikea.
So they realised that they are trapped.
They did son, they did but, Dündar Bey
ordered Batur for the attack.
It's obvious that he wants to shine
Batur's star.
He's doing the right thing.
He's even late.
Batur will do what's needed eventually.
He needs to know how to stand when he's
up against Alişar.
My Bey. Alişar Bey is back from Konya.
Thank you, Boran.
And my Bey, Edebali...
... is settling in Yenipazar with
his friends.
My Bey, now is the right time.
We shall take off.
Keep your eyes on Alişar's mansion. I want
to know who visits him.
Your wish is my command, my Bey.
Bamsı Bey, I'm going to Yenipazar. Keep an
eye on the Tent.
Thank you, my Osman.
What is it Aygül? Did something
block your sun?
Why do you use such dark colours?
Once we take care of our troubles, white
flowers will blossom on our carpets.
Do we cause you trouble, Zöhre?
Just say it.
You're like a splinter, but I'm not
talking about you, Selcan Hatun.
Stay calm.
Then who are you talking about?
Who is causing you trouble?
It's not mine, but everyone's
trouble, Selcan Hatun.
Since Edebali came, we keep
arguing in the Tent.
It's not because a friend came...
... but because you glorify yourself
since your husband became a Bey.
Pity. You're both blind, and you've
forgotten all about our traditions.
Why would his aunt try to arrange
marriage, instead of his uncle?
You went. Seeing how Osman is doing, it
seems like you were denied.
Thant's what happens when you try to
handle things that are not your job.
You say he, I say my son.
If my son wants something from me, I'll
do it no matter what.
That's right. Sheikh Edebali didn't
allow it.
That's right. My Osman is upset.
But, a valiant goes through trouble,
takes shape with love.
I know my valiant. He won't let
go of this.
I'm upset. I'm upset that his father
worked so hard for him.
Why is that?
While Ertuğrul Gazi's son is
chasing ladies...
... my Batur is attacking the
enemy's caravan.
They say it for a reason.
A real valiant can be seen in the fields.
You will pay for this!
From now on, swords rule, commander.
We won't stop until you're out
of breath in your castle. Know that.
Now go, tell them Dündar Bey's son Batur
has seized the caravan.
Separate the gold and the
ornaments, Ongun Alp.
Yes, Batur Alp.
Brothers! It's been a long time since we
last attacked an enemy caravan.
From now on, they will fear our wrath!
We will be sudden, like death.
Allahu Akbar!
(Allah is the greatest!)
Long live Dündar Bey!
- Selamın Aleyküm.
- Aleyküm Selam.
What is going on, why is it this crowded?
We're waiting for Sheikh Edebali.
- Thank you.
My Bey. Now is the time.
Let's go from the back.
You keep an eye out, brother. I'll take
care of the rest.
Yes, my Bey.
Welcome, my Sheikh.
- Welcome!
- Welcome.
Selamın Aleyküm.
(Peace be unto you)
Aleyküm Selam.
Bismillah.
(In the name of Allah)
Friends, my friends call me "my Sheikh".
My name is Edebali.
We have come here to trade,
taking the example of our prophet.
My friends are called Ahis.
Many more of my brothers are on
their ways.
We believe in...
Day of Rising...
which everyone will get their fair shakes.
From now on...
our aim is justice.
We wish that...
the bazaar's order will continue.
We wish that the right one's words ...
will be more important than
the powerful one's.
We wish poor people will be full up.
We wish everyone to help each other.
We wish people to buy cheap goods...
and eat them.
We'll support this bazaar from now on.
- May it be good for us.
- Amin.
Welcome, princess. Here.
Princess...
I rolled out the red carpet for
your beautiful eyes.
Welcome to my mansion.
Your mansion has a legendary beauty...
Alişar Bey.
It used to be a mansion but...
it became a palace when a
princess like you came.
I did all of this for you.
Roses are the princesses of the flowers.
Here. Come.
My Sheikh...
come, Osman Bey.
What do you want from me?
Is it a wish...
or a breath?
A wish.
What if I don't provide it?
Then...
I'll wait.
I'll wait for the time.
Waiting is the ability of
Dervish, Osman Bey.
You'll reach the end of your rope...
your mind will blow up...
and you can't resist it.
Waiting isn't for people...
who are immature.
Waiting...
is the ability of people...
who have self preservation.
You beat people...
but...
this wrestle...
is beyond your depth, Osman Bey.
I wrestled many times.
I fought.
I've never beaten.
But...
Now I have.
Thanks.
My favorite smell.
Jasmine.
It doesn't suit everyone's skin.
You know well about scents, Alişar Bey.
Smell.
Does it suit me?
- What do you want, Sofia?
- We love the same things with you, Alişar Bey.
The smell of the flowers and...
the sound of the gold.
I have both of them.
Do you support Osman and Edebalı or...
the things you love?
What's your problem with Osman?
Tell me.
I care about neither
Osman nor Kayıs.
We were going to
do the thing that Mongols couldn't...
if Osman wasn't around.
We were going to stop Edebalı.
What's your problem with Edebalı?
Edebalı will be a problem for my state...
when he settles here.
Just like he is now, for your state.
Alişar Bey.
I want you to stop Edebalı.
If we join hands, we can hold
the fire and...
rechase it.
Don't let Edebalı...
poison our friendship.
How will I trust you, Sofia?
What is it?
Sir...
Batur, Dündar Bey's son, raided
the Byzantine caravan.
He murdered the soldiers
in the Byzantine lands.
Damn it!
He endangered my lands!
Don't you see it?
You see it, too, Alişar Bey.
Edebalı first poisoned Osman Bey, and now
Dündar Bey.
You...
Do you still think how will you trust me?
I said what's necessary.
If the tax for Mongols decline...
they won't keep you here.
You'll be a shoe sole for
Mongols' shoes...
not Sultan's shadow...
Alişar Bey.
Princsess...
Wait for me tonight. I'll visit you.
Won't you look at me too, Bala?
Allah knows.
You should too.
I promised you.
I'll live for it, Osman.
But, my father's words are above mine.
If he's unwilling, I can't do anything
- Don't come again.
- Bala!
What are you saying?
How will I live without
looking at your...
face and eyes?
I entrusted my heart to you.
I'm here as long as you keep it.
If you give up, I won't resent.
Then...
it's my promise.
You should know that.
Wherever you go...
I'll be behind you.
I promise.
In the 99 names of Allah...
who has the power to create and who
fills our hearts with faith.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim. (In the name
of Allah, the compassionate, the merciful)
Beys of Kayı, I know...
you're wondering why I've
gathered you here.
I'm not wondering, Dündar Bey.
It's obvious what has happened
in Kulucahisar.
We wear our armours...
and we're waiting for your order.
Samsa Bey is right.
It's time to fight.
Everything's clear now.
Our friends and foes are known.
Sergant Samsa is right.
It's time to fight, Dündar Bey.
Bamsı Bey.
Sergeant Samsa.
I know you're excited.
Now that you want to fight and
you want to loot...
let me show you.
Baturalp!
Bring them.
What are these, Dündar Bey?
Loots that Baturalp gathered
with his own hands.
My brave son showed the world...
how to raid a caravan.
Just like he saved Osman...
he displayed a great valour.
Speaking of him, where is our Osman Bey?
Isn't he invited?
Osman isn't on tent.
He is busy.
Gündüz Bey couldn't tell much.
Osman Bey has a more crucial work.
You know, Selcan Hatun asked for the
girl's hand for Osman but...
Sheikh Edebalı didn't accept.
Osma wants her and Edebalı doesn't accept.
It's none of your business, son.
Why do you say that, Bamsı Bey?
Osman is the son of my uncle...
we carry the same blood.
He wanted her so much...
Master Yannis, do you feel better?
I will if I hear good things from you, my
beautiful Sofia.
Don't worry then.
Alişar Bey's frailties are powerful
enough to make him a puppet.
- Do you know about caravan?
- Yes.
- Kayıs don't stop.
- They shouldn't.
- We'll make use of what they've done.
- How?
Our lovely ally, Alişar Bey...
will do what's necessary.
Then he'll come here. We'll
have dinner together.
But Kalanoz won't like it.
Kalanoz... Fool lover.
Then I'll give the most important
duty to Kalanoz.
He'll kill Edebalı.
Tell him that, Sofia.
Your command, sir.
Salvador.
It's your duty to punish Batur...
who've dared to raid our caravan.
I'll follow that Kayı bandit
like a shadow.
When I'm about to kill him, he'll
be scared.
Now, our matter isn't Osman, who suffers
the pangs of love...
it is my brave son Baturalp...
who is Kayı's hero.
He is the one who raided
unbelievers' caravan and...
who gathered these loots.
As long as I have son like him and...
I have these loots...
no one can put me out.
I can, Dündar Bey.
Alişar Bey.
Yes, Alişar.
Take these!
We gave you a tent...
to be in order..
not to be a bandit!
Since when are you raiding caravans?
These are loots.
Kulucahisar's goods.
How did you forget the treaty
we sealed together, Dündar Bey?
Where are the friendship and alliance?
What will I tell Sofia and Kalanoz?
There's no alliance, Alişar Bey.
They killed our Alps when
you're not around.
I don't care about your Alps.
I care about Seljuqs people.
Did someone let you raid there!
Do we need permission when we
do something to unbelievers?
This tent that you rule...
and manage...
and this tent that you have children in...
belongs to me!
You'll ask everything!
This tent belongs to Süleyman Shah.
It belongs to Kayıs, Alişar Bey!
Don't! Don't.
You can't order me, Batur!
Get out!
Now...
when I brought these loots to Kulucahisar...
and if I see that it lacks even a needle...
I'll kill you with a spear.
A spear!
You summoned me, my princess.
I have a gift for you, Kalanoz.
Your presence is my biggest gift.
Then you'll give me a gift.
What do you want?
Take it.
This sword will accompany your...
heroism.
When the time comes...
I'll marry...
this unique hero.
Nice words are like a song.
But, who do you want me to kill?
A big duty is given to you.
This sword...
will kill Edebalı.
Master Yannis gave the hardest duty...
to the most trustworthy soldier.
I'd do the same.
I'll take this sword as a marriage gift.
I'll rip Edebalı's heart off
and bring it to you.
Then...
we need a good plan...
that no one can prevent.
A good plan.
My Allah. Give me strength!
So that we can cut Alişar's hand and...
give it to him!
My Allah. Give me strength!
Bey.
Bey, Take a breath.
Your uncle doesn't approve it too.
Thank Allah that Osman wasn't here!
I hardly stopped myself.
How would we stop him?
You should support Dündar Bey.
He knows what to do.
And then you'll do what's necessary.
It can't be like that, Hatun!
It can't be like that.
The time will come and...
we'll slap Alişar Bey so hard that...
he'll understand why he shouldn't...
show off in Kayı tent.
He'll understand.
Boranalp is coming, my Bey.
- My Bey.
- What is it, Boran?
You were right, Bey. Sofia went to
Alişar Bey's mansion.
- Where is he now?
- He went to the tent..
He raided the tent.
What are you saying, Boran?
He was angry with Dündar Bey for the raid.
What does it have to do with Alişar Bey!
- What did my uncle say?
- My Bey...
Alişar Bey slapped Batur in front of the
Beys, he didn't even say anything.
Alişar Bey...
it's obvious that the castle
plans something.
They want to set on Alişar Bey.
Batur will suffer.
- Where is Batur?
- He got out of the tent.
He went somewhere.
I know where he is.
I hope he won't do anything insane.
- Where are my Alps?
- They're coming.
- Come to Şahin Hill.
- Your command, my Bey.
Dündar Bey!
Are the things I heard true?
Alişar Bey questioned all of you.
He slapped my Batur, and you
didn't say anything.
Keep your nose out of men's business!
I wouldn't approve that slap!
No one can slap Kayı's brave man!
- How can you...
- How can I remain silent, right!
He is the Banner lord, Hatun! Banner lord!
What will we do if he tell us to leave?
We can't go back!
There are Byzantine and Mongol beyond!
Don't you see that we're trying
to get organized?
After all...
Alişar Bey is...
Batur's brother is law.
He won't take it as a matter of pride!
He'll bear it.
He'll bear it!
It's a must.
I'm sure that...
he'll pay the price for that slap.
But...
we should do what's necessary now.
My dear Batur's mother...
What happened?
Pull yourself together.
How can Alişar Bey do something like
that, Selcan Hatun?
My son, my Batur...
Allah knows where he is.
How he is.
Alişar Bey slapped
Batur, apparently, but...
Alişar Bey will regret it.
However, I am concerned about Batur,
Zöhre.
You know him very well.
He is from your blood.
Tell me.
Would he do something crazy?
If it is being about man, each one of
our man is the same, Selcan Hatun.
He doesn't hurt himself, in sha Allah.
He doesn't make me worry, in sha Allah.
Come on. Pull yourself together.
We need to stand.
You need to stand.
You need to pray and stand.
You meet your son as soon as possible,
in sha Allah.
In sha Allah.
May you relieve as soon as possible.
And the unity of our tent continues,
in sha Allah.
In sha Allah.
Efendis!
(Gentlemen!)
Alişar Bey.
Don't you respect the Banner lord
of Seljuq?
Even in my lands, in my bazaar.
What a tactlessness?
Sit, Alişar Bey.
In Baghdad Cemetery, Behlül dug
a grave and fell asleep in it.
Sultan Reşit ordered to find him
immediately.
Soldiers started to search for Behlül.
They finally found him.
They woke that poor up by poking him
with their spears.
You know, it's Behlül.
He closed his eyes and opened his mouth.
Asked: "why did you wake me up?"
Soldiers took him to Sultan at once.
While smiling, Sultan asked...
"You argued with soldiers for waking you
up"
What is the reason?
Behlül started talking.
He said he was a Sultan in his dream.
He said he had soldiers,
a palace, servants.
Everything was ruined when
they woke me up.
Sultan Reşit laughed.
He said it was just a dream.
Behlül looked at Sultan,
then the soldiers.
And he said, "Then, tell me, Sultan."
"What is the difference between my reign
in the dream and your reign here?"
He said, "Mine has ended when I woke up,
yours will end when you die."
Then...
Tell us, Alişar Bey.
You rely on your soldiers and power, so
you try to question us.
Is it worth a Sultanate which will end
someday?
Think about it...
Is that tactless you, who comes in
without permission and wait for respect...
or is it us who ignored a mortal?
I came here to question you about coming
here without my permission.
However, I see that I will be pleased to
have you here.
Forgive me, my Sheik.
Alişar Bey, you know that...
in that raid, my friends have been
martyred.
My Ahi brothers died here.
Now it is also our land.
We know Ahi order and Ahi tradition.
Your essence gives us power and makes our
bazaar mighty.
brought to you by kurulusosman.online
You can't order me!
I'll take revenge, Alişar!
You disgraced me in front of my Beys!
Onur Alp! Sercan Alp!
Leave me alone! Don't come!
You heh!
I'll not leave you alone here.
Let's finish our thing.
Attack.
Hold on brother!
My brother!
Osman... Attack!
- Brother.
- Eyvallah (thank you) brother.
Kill them already!
Allah is eternal!
Losers!
It's nice to see you, Osman.
I'll take revenge for Juan.
Leave him to me, brother.
Not only Juan, but we
also killed all your dogs!
Now, it's your time.
Die!
- Batur Bey, are you okay?
- I am fine, Abdurrahman Ghazi.
Then, we can watch the show.
Leave a bit to us.
We won't get any, brother.
- Are you fine, brother?
- Yes, brother. I am alive thanks to you.
You are my brother.
I'd do anything for you.
Eyvallah, my brother.
(Thank you.)
- Boran.
- Yes, my Bey?
Take Batur to the tent with Boğaç and
Erkut.
Let Bamsı Bey know that we have
Aybars' murderer.
Eyvallah (okay) my Bey.
What are we going to do with this dog,
Osman Bey?
We will take him to the cave.
He'll tell us about his owners.
My Bey. I don't understand.
We went there angrily and we are returning
calmly now.
Where did I come from, Nizamettin?
- Konya, my Bey.
- Hah, at least you know that.
I'll tell you what you don't know.
Konya is not in good condition.
I am here to represent Sultan, but...
I saw in Konya that there is no Sultan
to represent.
Mongols occupied there.
Then, what should we do, Nizamettin?
You know the best, my Bey.
The best thing to do is to be the Sultan.
Being Sultan requires money,
money requires good craftsmen.
Now, tell me. Is there any better
craftsman better than Ahis...
in this country?
No, my Bey.
Then, we know what we have to do.
Edebalı will produce and sell...
and Alişar Bey will gain money.
You shall please them.
Who is this young one, Nizamettin?
She is Sheik Edebalı's daughter
Bala Hatun, my Bey.
Bala.
Enough.
Wait.
They can hold their breath a long time.
Let's try this.
There is no easy way to die for you!
Is this the head of my son's murderers,
my Osman?
Yes, Bamsı Bey.
My Osman.
Tell me.
Tell me, infidel.
Did you give my Aybar's death order with
this tongue?
Tell me, infidel!
Do you hear your allies with this ear?
Do you see with this eye?
Did you kill my Demirbüken with this hand?
Speak, infidel!
Speak!
How can you...
be so dishonored?
My Osman! My Osman, are you done
with him?
I'll give him to you when I'm done,
Bamsı Bey.
Give him to me when you are done,
my Osman.
Edebalı's Ahis will bring benefit to our
bazaar. What a smart move, my Bey.
Not only Bazaar. Edebalı will bring
benefit to my house too.
What's in your mind, my Bey?
She is nice.
I liked Bala Hatun quite a lot.
I witness how beautiful creatures Allah
creates.
And this gazelle comes across with a
hunter like me.
But, my Bey, your marriage with
Aygül Hatun is near.
- Do you give her up?
- Why would I?
I am Alişar Bey.
I have room for everyone.
Bey's daughter in a room, Sheik's
daughter in another room.
Isn't this better?
Masha Allah, you are like a lion,
my Bey.
But I don't think both Edebalı and Dündar
Bey would accept this.
If they don't, Dündar Bey's daughter is
not important.
My mansion needs someone like Bala Hatun
who is beautiful, diligent and nimble.
Let's wait.
Everything has a time.
Enough.
Please, stop.
- Tell us!
- Please...
My death won't be good for you.
I know a lot.
I'll speak.
I'll help you save Edebalı if you
forgive me!
Tell me!
Is Edebalı in danger?
I'll tell you if you let me live.
I will.
Tell me.
Tell me!
Tonight, Edebalı...
What will happen to Edebalı tonight?
Kalanoz will kill Edebalı with his men.
Look at me, if you are playing,
you will beg to die...
instead of begging to live!
- You'll let me live, right?
- I will...
But, I don't know about Bamsı Bey.
Don't give me to him.
Please, Osman Bey.
If this infidel is right, it's hard to get
there on time.
It's pitch-black outside. Horses are tired.
It will be hard to get there, Osman Bey.
- May Khidr be with us
- Amin.
Let's go there at once.
Go, valiant.
It's a flawless table, Princess.
Your guest will like it.
Everything in this castle is to satisfy
us, Helen.
Come here, Bannerlord Alişar Bey.
Come and tell us what you are going to
do for us.
Princess Sofia is waiting for you,
Alişar Bey.
- Get well soon, Commander.
- Thank you, Alişar Bey.
We'd get injured in battlefield back then,
now we do while defending our caravan.
Welcome, Alişar Bey.
Thank you, Princess.
I brought Dündar Bey and Batur into line.
In front of every Kayı Beys.
The goods that you lost during the attack
have been brought to your castle.
From now on, I take precautions to
not let something like that happen.
Don't worry.
I have never doubted that you'd do
what is necessary, Alişar Bey.
Here is my gift, Princess.
You are very kind.
It's nothing in the light of your
beauty, but...
you will make me happy if you wear
this as a symbol of our friendship.
What a right choice.
Like all of your other choices.
Here.
I prepared sherbet for you.
I hope you like it.
Your table represents you, Princess.
Flawless.
I am embarrassed about what happened.
You did your best to meet the harm,
Alişar Bey.
You don't need to be embarrassed.
A simple caravan is not important while
there is our allied power...
that we'll use from now on.
- The day has come, finally.
- Where are the wardens, Nizamettin?
I called them here. They'll be here soon.
Take care of them.
- What about Edebalı's house?
- The stone house in the other street.
When you kill wardens, the bazaar will
be defenseless. Edebalı is easy.
His daughters Bala and Gonca are home.
And two dervishes of his.
One of them is the one who introduced
himself as father Marcus.
Nizamettin.
This is going to end tonight.
If something goes wrong, you'll
be responsible.
There will be nothing wrong, Commander
Kalanoz. Be sure about this.
They will perform ablution first.
They read Quran before going to bed.
They'll sleep and close the doors.
They think that the Devil
can't open the doors.
Osman.
How did you know we were coming?
Salvador, dog of Yannis, whispered to me.
Now he's trying to persuade
Bamsı Bey to keep his head!
I can still feel the warmth of
the wounds we opened in you.
Just wait, Kalonos, you will burn
in the wounds you opened.
Those who come unnoticed,
sleep without a bed, don't you know?
Seeds of the infidels!
Do it, Osman.
Do it!
I told you, you will
burn in those wounds.
This is for Demirbüken!
And this is for Kanturalı!
Osman!
It has just begun, Osman.
I'm in no rush.
I will first deal with Sofia, then
with the dog that's her father.
You... You are not strong enough, Osman.
You are nothing compared to us.
Until I ride the horse of
doom and wreck Kulucahisar...
... until I spill the poison
out of Sofia's teeth...
... and stab Yannis in the
monastery he came from...
... dying is forbidden to me!
My Aybars...
... never liked weapons.
He told me in his childhood, "You can take
weapons father, I'll pick up the pencil."
Back then, I had muscles like the breast
of a buffalo, and chest like a stallion.
I was strong, I was strong.
Other Beys would send their children
to test their skills at weapons...
... but Aybars would just
say "I don't want weapons."
They told me then...
..." countries are taken with weapons,
but held with a pencil.
I said "Okay. I will keep my weapon,
you can keep your pencil, son."
But, you infidels just
couldn't allow that, could you?
They started harassing my
Aybars from his childhood.
They didn't let him study!
After deciding there was no other way...
... he mounted his horse, and
took his weapon on his hand.
My son was a valiant warrior.
He sided with my Osman...
... and they became a mountain together.
Once...
... my Aybars stood
in front of me.
He said, "Father.". I said,
"Tell me, my brave son!"
He said, "Father."
" I have a request."
I said, " You can wish
anything, my son!"
I said "Your father would
make far places close...
... and make impossible
things possible for you."
I said...
" If you want, your father would spit
fire, and melt mountains of iron for you!"
"I'm in love." ...
...he said.
"I'm in love."
My heart was like an erupting volcano.
"Okay!" I said. "Okay! It's tradition!"
The lover will take the one he loves.
It's me, Tursun Efendi.
Listen to me, Tursun Fakı.
What are you doing, Osman Bey, are you
trying to get what you need like this?
It's not about me, Tursun Fakı,
everyone's lives are in danger.
My Sheikh!
First, you made our store a marketplace.
Then you became an armour for our death.
Now, I ask you again, Osman Bey.
Is it a wish...
... or a breath?
I said "Would Sheikh Edebali...
... accept me in...
... If I weep blood from
my eyes, and rip my chest?
- And did I?
- You didn't.
"If I, like Eyüp (Prophet)...
... was attacked by wolves...
... weep blood, like Yahya (Prophet)...
... prayed on Mount Tur...
... like Musa (Prophet)...
... would Sheikh Edebali accept me in?"
I said.
- Did I?
- You didn't.
"If I be a fish like Yunus...
... stay in a well for days, like Yusuf...
... weep blood for Yusuf, like Yakup...
... would Sheikh Edebali accept me in?"
I said.
- Did I?
- You didn't.
I'm embarrassed and ashamed for
eternity, Sheikh Edebali.
Now I can finally say it. My only wish is
your blessed breath.
Your one prayer.
There are Abdalans, who come to us,
dispersed by love.
There are Bacıyans, who think of serving
us as their duties.
But, your only purpose should be holy
war, in the name of Allah.
As long as you fight this holy war...
... our breaths will be with you, son.
Thank you, Sheikh Edebali.
Your purpose is to prevent Oğuz
Clans oppression...
... in the name of Allah.
You shall be one of Gaziyans, with
this purpose.
A man doesn't put responsibilities behind
for love, for passion.
Being the ruler of Gaziyans will
suit you better.
My father described you as Oğuz's light.
Even if it costs us our lives, we won't
let this light go off.
As Allah tested Adam with getting
close to the tree...
... Allah tests Adam's children with...
... patience and gratitude under every
circumstance, Osman Bey.
Because in the world of reason, whatever
happens to a person...
... happens for a hidden reason.
With patience and gratitude...
... under your mighty shadow...
... we could take shape.
Thank you for that.
He has begun taking shape on your
door, my Sheikh.
Osman Bey.
Bala Hatun.
Sheikh Edebali's breath and prayers are
with us, thankfully.
Thankfully.
It's patience from now on. We shall
patiently wait for your father to call us.
To wait, we have both hearts...
... and love.
- Now if you excuse me.
- Of course, Osman Bey.
May Allah guide your way.
Fire everywhere, poisonous snakes
everywhere.
Where does Batur go unannounced like this?
His pride was injured in front of
everyone.
You embarrassed him!
It was his uncle who hit him.
Not a stranger!
If you don't say anything, he'll do
it again.
My Batur didn't say anything wrong.
Why would that coward hit him?
Kayı Bey's son gets slapped by a fancy Banner
Lord who puts cinnamon juice on his beard.
My Allah, protect us.
May I come in, Dündar Bey?
Come in, Boran Alp.
Batur! My Batur, my valiant what
happened to you?
Batur! My son.
I was ambushed in the woods.
Osman saved my life.
Master Yannis.
- Kalonoz.
- What happened?
We found his corpse in front
of the castle, sir.
Useless fool!
- How did it happen?
- We don't know, sir.
There are Muslim hair on him and lots
of scars on his body.
Sofia...
Does Sofia know this?
Princess Sofia is dining with Alişar Bey.
She doesn't know yet.
- Good.
- What are your orders?
Dress Kalonoz with his own clothes. Then
he should go to Alişar and Sofia.
Alişar Bey shall see the Turks cruelty
and how noncompliant they are.
From this day on, I promise you
for your safety, Princess.
Besides, I ordered another caravan
for you.
They should be here soon. Caravans, and
your counters at the bazaar...
... are under my protection.
The support of a powerful Banner Lord
like you always make us happy.
But...
... if Edebali dominates the bazaar, that
will be bad for all of us.
Edebali and dominating the bazaar...
Not possible while I'm around, Princess.
Edebali and his Ahis will get the
bazaar moving.
But, under my shadow.
And as long as we gain something
from them.
How will you stop them?
How?
He was ambushed while returning
to the castle.
Who would do this?
He was fighting the Turks.
Osman! Osman did this, I know it!
This attack was not just aimed at us.
This is an uprising which disregards you,
Alişar Bey.
I want Osman's life.
"Valiants don't protect dishonest ones."
I said.
He turned, looked...
... then smiled in such a way that...
... my ancestors from the savannas flash
right before my eyes.
He looked at me in such a way that...
... he had Hamza's looks in Uhud.
Why didn't you say "Stop."?
Who tells someone who's going to holy
war to stop, you fool?
"Go!" you say! So he doesn't worry about
the ones left behind!
"Go!" you say. So that their essence
leaves their body!
"Don't leave my Osman alone." I said.
Just so we can call these lands, which
bullies like you wander about, home...
... sacrifice yourself, I said.
He's gone. He's gone.
He's gone.
He didn't come ever again.
He made his father, a martyr's father.
He made the lands his gravestone is
laid upon, our home.
"Valiants don't protect dishonest ones."
I said.
It's time to stay alarmed.
Bamsı is a martyr's father!
Bamsı is a martyr's father! Bamsı has
become a martyr's father!
Now...
Now it's time.
Thank Allah a thousand times...
... I will take my son Aybars' revenge.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim
(In the name of Allah, the merciful and compassionate.)
Bamsı Bey!
I don't want to die without
becoming a Muslim.
My love.
I will take your revenge.
I swear, I won't let Osman go without
making him pay for this!
Kalonoz's spirit will reach peace when we
reach our goals, my daughter.
My dear daughter Sofia, we'll hold tight
to take Kalonoz's...
... and other fallen ones' revenges.
In our cause, what suits us is not
shedding tears...
... but holding on tightly against those
who did this.
We will make them pay for this!
Now that I saw you side by side like the
mountains, I am happy.
And Allah shall make you happy.
The enemy set traps like the
weasels they are.
But thankfully, my brother Osman was
there to save me with his claws.
We did, for now, brother.
We shall stay no more, uncle. Wolves to
wolves, dogs to dogs.
Everyone learned the truth.
The snakes in Kulucahisar, that Banner
Lord in Eskihisar...
... are our enemies.
What does Alişar Bey have to do
with this, Osman?
Your aunt is right, my nephew. And don't
you know?
Soon a wedding tent will be established.
Before Alişar attacked the Tent, he
talked with Sofia in his mansion.
It's obvious who filled him with
the anger.
Osman! What are you saying, brother?
Yaman! Drums are being played.
Who is coming?
Your death is here, Dündar Bey!
Things have gone out of control. What do
you think you're doing Alişar Bey?
Ask that to Osman, not me!
Osman, I'm arresting you for killing the
Kulucahisar Castle's Commander Kalonoz.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com